- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[Caws]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hey!
Eh!
Go!
[Murmurs]
[Thumping]
[Clamor]
[Sputtering]
Good morning. Uncle Donald.
You can't wear this
to your job interview.
[Sputtering] My uniform!
You gotta dress for the job you want.
not the job you have. which is no job.
Wah!
Huey. don't touch the stove. It's hot!
But it's a big day. and a big day
calls for a big breakfast!
[Deflating Sound]
Bleh!
I'll get the iron.
Ouch! Ooch.
[Sputtering]
Stop helping me. And
put on your life vests!
What if the boat goes down
while the babysitter's here?
BOTH: Yes. Uncle Donald.
Where is that babysitter?
Where are you?!
What?
I didn't give you a new address.
Well. what time can you get here?
I... don't know.
Crazy old bird.
Where can I find another
babysitter at 10:00?
- 10:00?!
- You gotta go!
Aah!
I can't just leave you!
We can survive for a couple of hours!
A couple of hours. Uh... well. okay.
But just keep those life vests on!
[Engine Starts]
Where's Dewey?
- Sleeping.
- Who's Dewey?
Who's Dewey?
All right. boys. we'll get
to Cape Suzette and back
before anyone realizes we're gone.
So long. Dorkburg! Hello...
Uncle Donald?
What... What's up?
I can't leave you boys
alone for one minute!
You were supposed to get
him out by 10:00. Hubert!
You were supposed to signal before
you started the boat. Dewford!
We never get to do anything!
Boys. if we want to
keep our home afloat.
we've all got to do
things we don't want to do.
[Beeps]
Destination: McDuck Manor.
McDuck Manor? As in Scrooge McDuck?
The bajillionaire?
You're finally gonna sell us.
I'm not gonna sell... He owes me.
We're gonna meet Scrooge McDuck?
- That guy's amazing!
- What!
I heard he's so epic
he defeated a rock giant
and carved a statue of
himself out of its legs!
I heard he's so smart he solved
the mystery of the chupacabra.
Turns out it was just a shaved bear!
I heard that he's so rich
he only hunts for treasure
to swim in it!
All right. take it down a notch.
It's only a couple of hours.
A couple of hours with the
most exciting duck in the world!
With business expanding
in the Spoonerville
and St. Canard markets. noted
in Appendices C. G and 5F.
we're also cutting funding
to unnecessary departments:
Historical Research. Experimental Tech.
Deep Sea Exploration...
Fantastic.
Back in the bin with ya.
See you tomorrow. [Sighs]
[Clinks]
[Grunting]
[Tires Squealing]
[Barking]
Just another day at
the office. eh. Mr. McD?
[Laughs] Been there.
I don't have an office. per se.
but in some ways the road is my office.
Hey. that's deep. I
gotta write that down.
[Crash]
Geh! Eyes on the road. McQuack!
Every dent is coming out of your salary.
Absolutely. Hey. ya read about
that crazy snowstorm on
the Drake Barrier Reef?
I'd hate to fly into that one.
See. I'm a bit of a
pilot. and. uh... Oh. okay.
Divider... there you go.
Hit the brakes!
[Tires Squealing]
Ech.
Why aren't we moving?
Mrs. B.. open up!
I need to get out of here before...
[Honking]
he shows up.
Hey! Jettison that jalopy
from my driveway this
instant. ya deadbeat!
Donald Duck.
Uncle Scrooge.
- Uncle Scrooge!
- [All Jeering]
So. you're looking good.
Still living on that boat?
Yup. Still a trillionaire?
[Bird Calls]
Good. good.
So...
Jettison that jalopy
from my driveway this
instant. you deadbeat!
Oh. here we go!
Giving orders like he's the
richest duck in the world!
I am the richest duck in the world!
Now move!
I would love to!
It just so happens I
have a job interview.
So why are you standing there yelling?
Mrs. B. said that you
would watch the boys!
Can you do that without losing them?!
- Of course I can!
- Fantastic!
Thank you so much!
You're welcome! Wait. what now?
[Car Door Slams]
Huey. Dewey. Louie. meet Scrooge McDuck.
Remember. no tricks.
no lies. no trouble.
ALL: Yes. Uncle Donald.
I wasn't talking to you.
Whoa!
Talk to your nephews.
Ew.
[Startles]
So. do children still
like marbles or...?
Are you really our uncle?
- How old are you?
- What's your net worth?
What's the deal with
you and Uncle Donald?
Is that fork real silver? Can I have it?
- How come you never visit?
- 'Cause you're so old and moving is so hard?
You owe us. like. a lot
of birthday presents.
You used to be a big deal!
Whatever happened to you?
Beakley!
Aah!
You agreed to watch them.
Watch them.
Huey. Louie. the third one...
Please do not leave the
designated play area.
- [Clinks]
- A gift from your great-uncle.
You will return them
upon your departure.
He's counted them.
[Lock Clicks]
Great. Now we've got two boring uncles.
So. we're totally
ditching this room. right?
Yup. and I know just how to do it.
[Gasps]
[Grumbling]
"Used to be a big deal."
[Beating]
Stupid doorknob. come off!
Nailed it!
Can't believe that was your best plan.
Come on. guys. let's go
touch some expensive stuff.
- Aah!
- Dewey!
BOTH: Aah!
I'll put the marbles back. I swear!
Who sent you? Ma Beagle? Glomgold?
Answer me!
[Sobbing] Uncle Scrooge!
Uncle Scrooge?
Oh. my gosh. the nephews!
- Wait. you know us?
- [Grunting]
Of course! Researching Mr. McDuck
and his family is kind of my hobby.
- What?
- What are your blood types?
What's Donald really like?
Who's the evil triplet?
- Louie.
- Eh.
Tell me everything!
Um. we live with our uncle?
On a boat?
Go on.
Kinda it.
We're just a normal. boring family.
Normal. boring? Hah!
ALL: Ohh!
Whoa!
Huey. Dewey. and Louie Duck.
Scrooge McDuck's great-nephews
on his sister Hortense's side
with Quackmore Duck twice removed!
And you are?
Oh. right. Webby van der Quack.
My granny's the housekeeper.
Wait! Are we... friends now?
If we say yes. will you let us live?
[Scoffs] Good one. new best friend!
So. friend. what do you
do for fun around here?
Oh! I'm the best at fun.
Um... yah!
At least it's not the marble room.
[Grunting]
Come on. you blaggert.
You won't get the
best of Scrooge McDuck!
Hmm. A little spring cleaning?
Maybe. Maybe not. Read this.
Snow on the Drake Barrier Reef.
First time in 50 years.
That weather report aligns perfectly
with the Papia Prophecy.
A shift in currents may
present a pathway to Atlantis.
lost city under the sea!
This is because some children
made fun of you. isn't it?
Nonsense! I'm no has-been.
They're the has-beens.
I am an am-now.
Make a list!
Four oxygen tanks.
two pressure gauges. a pilot...
- I'm a pilot.
- A week's provisions.
- an experimental deep-sea sub...
- I'm a pilot.
And one secretary for an old man
who seems to have forgotten
that I am not his secretary!
So. eh. not interested?
I have enough excitement
caring for Webby.
Perhaps you should spend
some time with your family.
Oh. hang up my spats. become the
doddering old relic everyone thinks I am.
spinning yarns to those
loud-mouth young'uns
about the man I used to be?
You have avoided them for ten years!
Because family is nothing but trouble!
[Gasps] Oh.
I'm Scrooge McDuck.
I made my name being
tougher than the toughies
and smarter than the smarties.
And I made my money square. on my own.
no nephews. no family.
no one helped me there.
and I don't need help now. and...
[Clattering]
Beakley. a little help.
Maybe they're right.
Whoo! Vent crawl!
[Both Groan]
You don't get out much. do you?
Eh. Granny's a bit overprotective.
She trains me to be ready for anything.
but then she says I've got
everything I need in here.
But one day. I'm gonna see the world.
I'm gonna be an explorer!
I'm gonna eat a hamburger.
We could bring you a hamburger.
You really are my best friends.
Welcome to the Wing of Secrets!
I knew it!
Dewey. check it out!
Yeah. whatever.
The Gong of Picchu.
Hit it three times to
unleash unspeakable evil.
Uh. what are you doing?
Calling dibs on stuff!
What? Scrooge is. like.
he's. like. super old.
Oh. careful! Medusa gauntlet.
One touch can turn
organic matter to stone.
[Imitates Solidifying]
I'm gonna call this one a maybe.
This place is incredible!
It's fake.
Is that Uncle Donald?
Oh. yeah. he was Mr. McDuck's sidekick!
- Dewey's right.
- Totally fake.
Uncle Donald has never
done anything cool.
What? Donald Duck is one of the
most daring adventurers of all time!
[Stuttering]
[Phone Rings]
[Shiny Ring]
Bop bop.
Bop.
Yo. chung chung!
Bop bop!
[Exclaiming]
[Yelling]
This has got to be a fake.
And I bet everything else is. too.
That's not true!
What about this picture with chupacabra?
- Photoshop.
- This treasure chest?
Probably bought it at an auction.
This... g-ghost?
You mean this Halloween decoration?
Curse ye. ye scurvy life-lubbers!
It's Captain Peghook. the
scourge of the River Styx!
It's real. It's really. really real!
[Evil Laughter]
The Deus Excalibur!
It won't rest until its target's slain!
But he's already dead!
[Gong Rings]
[Gasps] Do not let
anything else hit that gong!
Yep. I'm gonna sit this one out.
- Whoa! Aah!
- [Whinnies]
[Exclaims]
The headless man-horse!
That one feels self-explanatory.
[Rings]
That's twice!
One more. and something
terrible could happen!
What could be worse than this?
What in dismal downs
is going on in here?
ALL: There it is.
Why aren't you in your rooms?
[Screaming]
Rrrawgh!
- Aah!
- [Evil Laughter]
[Grunts]
[Neighs]
We've got this.
There are four of us and three of them.
If we... wait. never
mind. They teamed up.
[Evil Laughter]
Ah. good. that means only one target.
No. get back! You're old!
Oi. beastie! What's it gonna take
to shuffle you off to the afterlife?
The head of Scrooge McDuck!
[Cracking]
Would you settle for his hat?
[Roaring]
[Groans]
[Blade Rings]
There's your head.
I should've been more specific!
[Whinnies]
[Celebrating]
[Pounds]
We can explain.
We came down to your secret
museum to look for you.
because we love you?
Secret museum?
This is the gar-age!
The what?
Do you mean "garage"?
No. that's ridiculous.
If this is a garage.
then how do you explain
all this amazing stuff?
Like the garden hose of destiny?
Or Montezuma's stack of old magazines?
Or... Oh. yeah. it's a garage.
Unbelievable. I invite
you into my home...
You locked us in a room!
I gave you marbles!
All we wanted was to hand out with you!
Well. now you have.
and look at the mess it's got me!
I guess family is nothing
but trouble. right. Scrooge?
Everybody out!
- But we're...
- Out!
Well. what are you gaping at?
The curse is only activated if
you ring the gong three times
and... you already hit
it two times. didn't you?
[Crackling]
Pixiu. the Gold-Hunting Dragon...
Gold hunting? Sounds great!
Not when you're Duckburg's
single largest owner of gold!
[Sniffing]
Aah! Me money bin!
To your rooms!
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go eat a hamburger!
We're in!
Cool.
To be clear. I'm gonna
go catch the dragon.
The hamburger was a
metaphor from before.
Yeah. yeah. no. we get it. We get it.
But how are we gonna get up there?
I'm a pilot.
Ooh! Yeah! Ha ha!
It'll take more than some fancy flying
to shake old Scrooge.
you cash cannibal! Whoo!
Oh! Ow! Ugh!
It'll take more than a bruised spine
to shake old Scrooge.
you bad dragon-dog!
Take that!
No!
[Straining]
Whoo-hoo!
I thought I told you to go to your...
No time. We gotta work fast.
Webby. how do we stop it?
It's mystical. so we
need a mystical device.
like an oblivion mirror
or a medusa gauntlet. or...
- Like this?
- Grr.
What? I was gonna give it back.
Now. how do we get him down there?
Garden hose of destiny!
Launchpad. we need to swing him out.
Nosedive towards the bin
and get ready to pull up!
Yes. sir. random kid I just met!
- Any questions?
- Since when is Launchpad a pilot?
[Clinks]
You guys. our family is awesome!
ALL: Scrooge!
[Gasping]
[Cheering]
NEPHEW: Money! I knew it!
Aw. Family truly is the
greatest adventure of...
Oh. no. the ground!
[Crashing]
In the short time I've known you.
you've wrecked my home and my money bin.
unleashed several ancient evils.
and almost got me killed. twice.
Four times if you count each
monster as an individual time...
[Laughter]
That was incredible!
When you pulled me into the airplane
and said "No time!"
And who would have thought
of a Medusa Gauntlet?! Brilliant!
Oh. and then you swung me out
and pulled up just
in time and [Laughter]
You kids are nothing but trouble!
Curse me kilts. have I missed trouble!
I suppose I'll have
to keep an eye on you
to teach you how to get
into trouble properly.
- [Phone Ringing]
- You mean...?
Beakley! Clear my schedule!
I'm taking the wee ones on a field trip.
About time. And once again.
I am not your secre...
Now. let's go find the
lost city of Atlantis!
ALL: Yeah!
And no one tell your uncle Donald!
Who is that?
[Struggling]
You've got the job. Duck!
Seriously?
Oh. boy!
I'm a real accountant!
Accountant? That was filled yesterday.
You're our new sailor!
Welcome to Glomgold Industries!
Now. what do you know about Atlantis?
♪ Life is like a hurricane ♪
♪ Here in Duckburg ♪
♪ Racecars. laser. airplanes ♪
♪ It's a Duckburg ♪
♪ We might solve the mystery ♪
♪ We'll rewrite history ♪
♪ Ducktales ♪
♪ Every day they're out
there making ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Tales of daring-do ♪
♪ And good-luck tales ♪
♪ T-t-t-teaser grows behind you ♪
♪ Got a stranger out to find you ♪
♪ What to do. just climb
onto some ducktales ♪
♪ Whoo-ooh ♪
♪ Every day they're out
there making ducktales ♪
♪ Tales of tarries bad and good ♪
♪ Not phony tales so
come into the Ducktales ♪
Glomgold Industries!
Take an idea.
Make it your own.
Better. faster. cheaper.
That's the motto
of the world's most beloved
Scottish billionaire duck!
Flintheart Glomgold!
Welcome. new employees.
to Glomgold Industries.
where our employees
are the greatest treasure of all!
[Clapping]
Glomgold! Glomgold!
Glom... Fine.
Enough glad-handing.
You're here because you're
the best of the cheapest.
With your help and my
carefully crafted master plan.
we'll find the fabled
lost Jewel of Atlantis
and finally make me the
richest duck in the world!
[Evil Laughter]
But first. here are your company IDs.
also good for 40% off life vest
rental in case of emergency.
Gabby McStabberson.
Hack and Slash Smashkinov.
Donald Duck.
Duck?
Duck?!
Ha! Now remember. bedtime is at 9:00.
And no sugar after 7:00. Oh. and...
I run a multi-trillion dollar business.
I can handle a few
juveniles for the weekend.
You just focus on this new job of yours.
Besides. we've got a
pretty low-key day planned.
Hoist the mainsail!
Other boat words. to
Atlantis! Dive! Dive!
- No. no. wait!
- Aye aye!
Launchpad. the hatch. Stop the...
Whoo-hoo!
Talk to your uncle.
Hey. Uncle Donald.
Nope. yeah. pretty boring.
We napped. rubbed
ointment on our joints.
old people stuff.
Oh. what about the dragon?
And the plane crash?
Whoops. 3:00 pm. Time for dinner. Bye!
Why didn't you tell him the truth?
You didn't tell your
grandma we were going
to a dangerous underwater city. did you?
I kinda sorta... didn't
tell her anything?
Webby. that's irresponsible!
She'll be worried sick!
Call your grandma this instant
and tell her that you are spending
the night at a friend's house. okay?
Lying: It's the responsible thing to do.
Launchpad. have you ever
piloted a sub before?
I sunk a helicopter in a wave pool once.
- Same thing?
- I've done more with less.
No matter. I'm back!
Unchartered territory.
Bold new discoveries!
Hello. bingo!
I love road trips!
I've got snacks. a playlist
of traditional sea chanties.
matching family road trip shirts!
I appreciate the enthusiasm.
but there's no time.
- But according to the travel itinerary...
- Boo!
Adventure isn't about
planning. it's about doing!
So. what can I be in charge of?
- The buzzsaw arm?
- No!
- Sonic cannons?
Hyper-dense zero-point
energy missiles
to pierce the scaly hide of a Kraken?!
None of those things are real things!
This is your first expedition.
so just stand back and watch an old pro
from a safe distance.
So what is this submarine equipped with?
[Whirs]
Seatbelts.
[Laughing]
Ha! Good one.
Classic Scrooge-Dewey banter.
the seasoned-but-tired explorer
passing the torch to his
cocky young successor.
I'm pretty sure he doesn't
actually know our names.
- I'm sorry. what?
- I think he called me her board ones.
Don't be ridiculous!
Hey. Scrooge! When are we
gonna set sail. Scrooge?
In a moment. Sonny Jim.
I will cram it down your throat.
Guys. lighten up! We're
on a deep-sea expedition
with Scrooge McDuck!
Mr. McQuack. chart a course.
Next stop. the lost City of Atlantis!
[Cheering]
At about 16:00 hours!
Shanty time!
♪ We love to sail the ocean ♪
♪ We love to sail... ♪
♪ Traveled all across the ocean ♪
[Singing In German]
♪ ...never have I been lucky ♪
[Snoring]
Driving! Piloting.
Driving. right?
Hey. Scrooge. First Mate Dewey here.
Your map's got us going the long way.
I can probably find a
shortcut if you just let me...
Uh-uh. lad. The shortest
distance between two points
isn't always a straight line.
Okay. but yes. it is.
so if you just go...
[Snoring]
Driving!
[Beep]
Huh?
Shortcut achieved!
He'll thank me later.
[Screaming]
[Roaring]
Oh. you kids'll be the death of me.
Dewey! Dewey will be the death of you!
Can we make a pit stop?
I have to use the
bathroom. but it's. um...
Occupied?
For the love of... It's
the middle of the ocean!
There are no pit stops.
How 'bout that conspicuously
unmarked tanker?
Ah. little Dewey's first steps.
And that's Huey in the playoffs.
He was the waterboy.
Oh. look! That's us
climbing the Grand Canyon...
display at the supermarket. Ah...
Ah. I miss them so much.
but we need this job.
So. tell me about your family.
I was raised by warrior monks
who spoke only the
language of the blade.
Uh...
[Beeping]
We've got intruders!
Scrooge?! What is he doing here?
Strange weather patterns
in a mysterious location
near treasure. Ha ha!
I knew he couldn't resist!
Hack. triangulate their sub's course!
We'll tail Scrooge
and steal the jewel out from under him!
The boys?!
Why. you get your hands... [Squawking]
I'm gonna kill him!
Ooh. better idea!
Nab the jewel and kill them all!
Somebody's angling for
employee of the month.
[Laughing]
[Thunder Crashing]
♪ ♪
SCROOGE: The Drake Barrier Reef.
Powerful currents
combined with rocky terrain
make it nearly impossible to navigate.
but on that rare
occasion when snow falls
above the reef. the currents cool.
allowing safe passage to...
[Snoring. Startling]
Are we there yet?
- I was just about to...
- Right side or the left side?
- If you'd just let me...
- Look! There that thing is!
We found it!
Whoa!
Yes. good. Atlantis.
"Ooh! Aah!"
Thanks for spoiling the moment.
The whole place is upside down!
Oh. well. that's a new one.
Whoa!
Just call your grandma
already! It's no big deal.
[Dialing]
Aah!
Remember. you're at a
friend's house. okay?
You got this.
[Rapidly] Hi. Granny.
I'm spending the night
at a friend's house so nothing is wrong!
Oh. you don't got this.
Ah-ha! Well. according
to these markings.
the Atlantines were so eager
to build an epic city of
wonders and death traps.
they didn't stop to figure
out a proper support structure.
and the whole thing fell into the sea!
You kids best stay by the
sub while I scout ahead.
Dewey ran in as soon as
you said "death traps."
DEWEY: Come on. Scrooge! We got this.
Boy! [Sighs. Mutters]
- [Blade Rings]
- [Donald Squawks]
Oopsie!
[Grunts]
Hmm?
Meh.
You made me miss!
Uh... if we get rid of them now.
we can't torture them later!
Brilliant! I want Scrooge alive
when I shove the Jewel of
Atlantis in his smug face!
He thinks his so rich and so Scottish.
but I'm wearing a kilt. McDuck. a kilt!
Dah! Lad!
I thought the traps
would get you for sure!
[Whirring]
Stupid upside-down temple!
Nothing cool about
walking under buzzsaws!
From now on. don't touch anything!
[Grunts]
[Screaming]
[Cracks Spine]
Maybe Atlantis was an
ambitious first outing.
[Ringing]
[Grunting]
Hi again. Granny!
Still at a friend's house.
Uh. her name? Sub... ina!
A totally real name for
a definitely real person!
[Beep]
Uh. good try.
- [Grunts]
- Launchpad. are you okay?
[Mumbling]
Ah. a little snake venom
never... [Gibbering]
Hi. nice to meet you!
I'm everybody's friend!
[Screaming]
Um. I've got to go to the bathroom.
I'll be right back!
[Groaning]
[Grunts]
Whoa!
Suspension bridge? Chasm?
Glowing blue mystical lasers?
Classic!
[Muttering] ...Scrooge. Wait
till I get my hands on him.
Even a basic death trap still
has the word "death" in the title.
[Squawking]
Oh. no.
We'll find another route.
It's not safe for amateur adventurers.
That sounds like a challenge!
I have to stress that
is not a challenge.
Is exactly what you say to
dissuade the weak of heart
from accepting the challenge!
Well. challenge accepted!
There's no challenge!
Dewey!
♪ Dew... ♪
[Screaming]
♪ Dewey. Dewey. Dewey. Dewey ♪
Huh? Aah!
♪ Dew. uh. Dewey. Dewey. Dewey ♪
[Quacks. Screams]
♪ Dew ♪
Oh. no!
♪ How does he Dewey it? ♪
♪ I don't know ♪
[Riffing]
[Quacking]
♪ Dew! And now you know ♪
Nailed it!
Sure. if you want to do it the easy way.
Why wouldn't you want
to do it the easy way?
You've got to work
smarter. lad. not harder.
Aah!
Ugh. "lad."
I don't call you "old
man" or "Scotty McTophat."
Respect your elder.
When you adventure
with Scrooge McDuck...
But I'm not.
You want me to adventure
behind Scrooge McDuck.
or wait by the sub!
I might as well be
back on the houseboat!
Because you have no
idea what you're doing!
So show me!
Give me a chance instead of lumping us
all together in the back
seat while you drive!
I'm not lumping you all together.
Oh. really?
Which triplet am I?
It's... Bluey?
Aah! Ow!
Ugh! Fantastic.
You see what I'm talking about?
You four find another way 'round!
We're going to... push onward.
apparently.
[Grunting]
[Sighs]
Why. this is no bathroom!
This shortcuts leads right
to the treasure chamber!
I don't even know why
I hired the rest of you!
Help him up!
Ow. Ouch! Owie! Owie!
Maybe I could just hire some family.
Then they'd have to listen to me.
[Laughs] There she is.
the Jewel of Atlantis!
[Cackling]
- Who's that?
- Flintheart Glomgold.
the poor man's version of me.
which. to be fair. still
makes him insanely rich.
[Cackling]
Load up the sub.
They've got Uncle Donald?
What?
Let go of my uncle!
- No.
- I wasn't prepared for that.
What are you doing here. Flinty?
What are you doing here. Scrooge?
I told you to keep the boys safe!
Ah. they're perfectly fine.
Oh. yeah? Where are the other two?
Back safe in the room with
the fire and the snakes.
- What?
- Ah. Scroogy.
I see you know my newest employee.
Your new job is with my sworn enemy?
I can't keep track of
all your sworn enemies!
Now. now. Donald has
been a model employee.
and an excellent prisoner.
Yeah! Wait. what?
Hiring my own nephew in
order to use him against me?
Now. that is good planning.
Have fun being the second
richest duck in the world...
for the next five minutes.
[Cackling]
I'd like to point out that
this trap was not my fault.
Junior Woodchuck Rule 841:
There's always another way around.
Hup!
- [Ringing]
- Hup!
Oh. no. no. no. no!
Oh. look! Uncle Hampus is here.
and he only speaks Swedish.
We don't want to be
rude. so... good-bye?
And you're done.
Yeah. you're never gonna
be able to back up that lie.
That was crazy!
Whoa!
Oh. hej. Beakley!
Subina... [Speaking Swedish]
[Glomgold Cackling]
Take 'em down!
Ojda.
We gotta stop the water!
[Quacking]
Oh. no.
[Sighs] I knew it!
I knew I couldn't
trust you with the boys!
Not the time. Donald.
Crazy old man!
All you care about is
your next adventure.
This is the Spear of
Selene all over again!
I was not responsible
for the Spear of Selene!
Stop! Scrooge was trying
to keep me out of trouble.
but I was so caught up in...
Why is there a lamp on the floor?
What?
Atlantis is upside down.
That means that lamp was
supposed to be on the floor
surrounded by all this treasure.
Attaboy. lad. Keep going.
But why would you surround that
thing with treasure unless...
BOTH: That's the real Jewel of Atlantis!
That thing lit up when
the trap was sprung.
I bet my bottom dollar it's the
power source that runs the city!
Uncle Donald. you
gotta let the room flood
so I can grab the jewel.
That's crazy!
I'm supposed to. what. let go?
Trust you?
Well. yeah. that's
kind of all you can do.
This is a surprisingly
insightful death trap!
[Quacks]
[Grunting]
[Panting]
Hey! We're gonna be okay!
[Grunting]
[Screaming]
Oh. yeah. those guys.
Huey and Louie!
Are doing okay!
[Grunting]
Wait! Where's Glomgold?
[Walkie-Talkie Crackles]
GLOMGOLD: Hey. team. Wanted to thank you
for keeping Scrooge's kin busy
while I escape with the
jewel and blow up Atlantis
with my most hated rival inside.
But I thought employees were
greatest treasure of all!
Don't be ridiculous!
Treasure is the
greatest treasure of all.
That's why it's called
treasure! Glomgold out!
We have to go!
- Huh?
- Mr. Duck.
Could we. um. maybe bum a ride with you?
That was some quick thinking.
You just may be an
adventurer yet. Dewey.
[Reporters Clamoring]
Aye. aye. Okay. Settle down.
Ha ha! Ladies and
gentlemen of the press.
it is with great pride that I.
Flintheart Glomgold. present...
The Jewel of Atlantis!
What?!
Is that Scrooge McDuck?
- Mr. McDuck...
- [Clamor Resumes]
An efficient. clean source of energy
that could power Duckburg for 50 years.
courtesy of your friends at
McDuck Water and Electric.
Ooh. Mr. McDuck. how do you respond
to claims by other Scottish billionaires
that they have the real jewel?
That bauble?
That's nice. but it's
obviously super cursed.
No. it's not!
[Splashing]
[Roaring]
[Screams] Curse you. McDuck!
- Webby. Uncle Hampus.
- How long?
Whole time.
Granny. I can explain.
Dear. you are safer in a
sunken city with Scrooge McDuck
than you are locked in
a vault in Fort Knox.
No more lies...
and you can go with
him wherever you like.
- Now. Donald. don't...
- Stop.
I admit I'm a little overprotective.
LOUIE: A little?!
No matter what I do.
these boys will get into trouble.
so maybe you could teach them
how to get out of trouble.
Uncle Donald?
It might be okay
if the boys saw you
every once in a while.
[Cheering]
Sometimes. like birthdays
or federal holidays.
- Nothing too...
- [Bang]
Ooh! I may have left the
engine running in the houseboat.
I may have a dozen or so spare bedrooms
in the mansion.
[Chuckles]
[Cheering]
There you have it.
Reclusive adventure capitalist
Scrooge McDuck is back.
with family in tow.
solving mysteries and rewriting history.
DONALD: Easy. A little to the left.
No. no. no. no!
Did I do it good?
[Laughter]
[Screams]
Mom?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
[Panting]
Take that!
[Laughing]
Dewey. don't yell at your target
before you fire.
You'll lose the element
of surprise.
- You'd better duck.
- [Yelling]
- Ahh! [Grunts]
- [Laughter]
"DuckTales."
All new Saturday. September 23
anywhere you watch
Disney XD.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm